zivity.com 2014-07-01

# Zivity

## Zivity values your privacy

## 1\. What this Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how Zivity treats personal information that Zivity collects and receives. As the Zivity site is only to be accessed by persons 18 years or older, we do not intend to collect any personal information from children under 13. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, including your name, email address, billing address, phone number, credit card information, birth date, and other information, that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Zivity does not own or control, or to people that Zivity does not employ or manage. 

## 2\. Information Collection and Use

Zivity gathers certain generic information with respect to customers' use of our web site, such as the number of unique visitors, the frequency with which they visit, and the areas on the web site that they favor. We only use this type of data in aggregate - that is, we look at the data on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us determine the extent to which our customers use certain parts of our web site which, in turn, enables us to make it as appealing as possible. We may also provide statistical information about how our customers collectively use our web site to advertisers, sponsors, and other companies with which we do business. We do this so they, too, can understand how often people use their areas of the site in order for them to provide you with the best possible experience. This statistical information does not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users.  

Zivity may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a Web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the site administrator may identify your computer and passively track its activities on the website. This unique number identifies your web browser to our computer system. A cookie will not allow a website to learn any personally identifiable information (such as your real name and address) that you have not otherwise disclosed. Cookies allow us to automatically remember your web browser when you visit our site or Service. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and they are currently used on most major Web sites. It is possible to adjust your Web browser preferences to alert you when a cookie is sent to your hard drive, or to refuse cookies altogether. While we do not require you to use cookies, keep in mind that certain sites and services may not function properly if you set your browser to refuse all cookies. 

## 3\. Disclosure Exceptions

Any information given to us shall be stored and managed with our best possible care, and will not be used in any ways to which you have not consented. We will not sell, rent or exchange such personality identifiable information to any other organization or entities, unless the user is first notified and expressly agreed to. Notwithstanding the above, we may indeed disclose personal information if required to do so in response to legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or when such disclosure is made for establishment or exercise of legal rights or in defending against legal claim or as otherwise required by law, including pursuant to 18 USC Section 2257. And, as we mention above, we may share with aggregated statistical information about the use of Zivity, its services and other future services. 

## 4\. Minors

If a parent believes that his or her minor child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via email or postal mail as listed below. We believe that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission. 

## 5\. Third Party Sites

Links on this website to other websites are provided as a convenience to you. Such linked sites are outside our control and responsibility and are not covered by this policy. If you use any such linked sites, you should consult the privacy policies posted on those websites. We may use companies to serve advertisements on some of our pages. These companies and advertisers may place and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours. We may use your information or allow advertisers or companies that serve advertisements access to your information to determine which advertisements you will see. This information may include your demographic information, geographic location, what content you access on our site, how you rate such content, language contained in your comments and other information. Our site contains links, including banner and other ads, to other Websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. Our site may also link to Websites that feature our trademarks and names along with trademarks and names of other companies. You should look at the privacy policy on that co-branded Website, as the co-branded Website may not be under our control. 

Applications you use or download from our site may contain third party digital rights management systems ("DRMS") which may allow for communication between your software and the third party and utilize security features (e.g., preventing distribution of or access to the applications in the event of unauthorized use). These DRMS are subject to their own license agreements and you agree that we shall not be responsible for any loss or damage of any sort relating to the use of the DRMS or your dealings with such third parties. The applications may also contain DRMS produced by us which allow for communication between the applications you use or download and our systems and which collect information describing your computer system in order to prevent illegal or unauthorized use of the applications. For reasons such as improving member experience and providing customized communications to our users, we may receive information about you from third party sources and our web logs and add it to the information that we have received from you. Web logs automatically record anything a web server sees, which may include e-mail addresses you enter into a form or pages viewed by a user at a particular IP address. 

## 6\. Information Sharing

We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties, aside from entities that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders or processing payment, that either are bound to comply with our privacy policy or have privacy policies that protect your information unless you have "opted-in" to such sharing. If you have previously opted-in to such sharing under a prior privacy policy version, you are still considered to have opted-in under this privacy policy. As stated, and whether or not you have opted-in, we may use third parties to accept and process orders for merchandise and products, including software, and such third parties may get access to your personal information for the purposes of providing services or products to you on our behalf. In addition, if you opt-out, we may share that information with third parties who send e-mails on our behalf so that they do not e-mail you. 

However, we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety. We may request demographic information from you (for example, your age, education level or household income) from time to time. We will not share that information in a manner that identifies you as an individual with any other entity, unless we let you know that at the time of collection or we have your permission. When we share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only. 

## 7\. Sale of Assets

In the event that Zivity is ever sold, acquired, merged, liquidated, reorganized, or otherwise transferred, we reserve the right to transfer our user databases together with any personally identifiable information contained therein, to a third-party acquiring Zivity' assets. In the event we do so, we will place a prominent notice of the sale on the homepage of our site, with links to information as to how you can change your privacy preferences. 

## 8\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change our privacy policy from time to time by updating the posting, provided however that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.   

NOTICE: The Federal Trade Commission provides [important information about safe surfing](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.shtm). 

### Contact Information

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info](mailto:info@zivity.com) References to Zivity in this Privacy Policy refer to Zivity, LLC, a Delaware limited liability company, and its affiliates.
